http://www.thefertilesoul.com/website-policy

HIPPA
Terms & ConditionsWelcomeWelcome and thank you for visiting the Fertile Soul website (“Website”) and reviewing our Terms of Use. The Fertile Soul, LLC, hereinafter collectively referred to as Fertile Soul, makes this Website, including all information, documents, catalogs, communications, files, text, graphics, and audio/visual files (collectively, the “Materials”) available for your use subject to the Terms of Use set forth in this document. It spells out what you can expect from us and what we expect from you.1. ACCEPTANCE OF TERMS OF USEPLEASE READ THESE TERMS AND CONDITIONS CAREFULLY. BY ACCESSING, USING, OR DOWNLOADING IN ANY WAY, WITHOUT LIMITATION, ANY MATERIALS FROM THIS WEBSITE OR MERELY BROWSING THIS WEBSITE, YOU AGREE TO AND ARE BOUND BY THESE TERMS OF USE.Fertile Soul reserves the right to change the Terms of Use at any time, without prior notice to any Website visitor (“User”). YOU ARE HEREBY ADVISED THAT YOUR CONTINUED USE OF OUR WEBSITE CONSTITUTES YOUR ACCEPTANCE OF THESE TERMS OF USE AND ANY SUBSEQUENT AMENDMENTS TO THESE TERMS OF USE. If you breach any of the Terms of Use, your authorization to use this Website automatically terminates, and any of the Materials downloaded or printed from this Website must be immediately destroyed.2. NON-TRANSFERABILITYA User’s right to use this Website is not transferable.3. MEDICAL DISCLAIMERSThe content of this Website, such as text, graphics, images, and other Material contained on this Website are for informational purposes only and are not intended in any way to substitute for professional medical advice, diagnosis, or treatment. Users are encouraged to develop a professional relationship with physicians and other medical practitioners and regularly consult with them to seek their advice. Never disregard professional medical advice or delay in seeking it because of something you have read, viewed, or heard on this Website. Users should review any information supplied to or on this Website with their own medical professional.While Fertile Soul attempts to prevent unauthorized access to our Website files, such access may occur.  Please consider that when deciding what personal medical information you choose to share on or through this Website.  Specific information about Fertile Soul policy with regard to medical information can be found in our HIPPA Policy. 4. INTELLECTUAL PROPERTY RIGHTSCopyright Information and Personal and Non-Commercial Use LimitationAll Materials and the compilation of all content included on this Website are owned or licensed by The Fertile Soul and protected by United States and international copyright laws. Copyright © 2004-2008. The Fertile Soul LLC.  All Rights Reserved. Fertile Soul does not claim ownership of Copyrights owned by third parties.You have been granted a license to view and use the Website Materials subject to these Terms of Use. Unless otherwise specified, the Materials on this Website are for your personal and non-commercial use. You may not sell or modify Website Materials or reproduce, display publicly or otherwise use the Website Materials in any way for any public or commercial purpose. Permission to reprint or electronically reproduce any document or graphic, in whole or in part, for any other purpose is expressly prohibited without prior written consent from The Fertile Soul. Users may not provide copyrighted or other proprietary information to Fertile Soul without permission from the owner of such material or rights. Users are solely responsible for obtaining such permission and for any damages resulting from unauthorized disclosures.Notice and Procedure for Making Claims under the Digital Millennium Copyright ActThe Digital Millennium Copyright Act (DMCA) provides recourse to copyright owners who believe that their rights under the United States Copyright Act have been infringed by acts of third parties over the Internet. If you believe that your copyrighted work has been copied without your authorization and is available on this Website in a way that may constitute copyright infringement, you may provide notice of your claim to Fertile Soul's Designated Agent listed below. For your notice to be effective, it must include the following information:1.     A physical or electronic signature of a person authorized to act on behalf of the owner of an exclusive right that is allegedly infringed; 2.     A description of the copyrighted work that you claim has been infringed upon; 3.     A description of where the material that you claim is infringing is located on this Website; 4.     Information reasonably sufficient to permit the service provider to contact the complaining party, such as address, telephone number, and, if available, an e-mail address at which the complaining party may be contacted; 5.     A statement by you that you have a good-faith belief that the disputed use is not authorized by the copyright owner, its agent, or the law; and 6.     A statement that the information in the notification is accurate and under penalty of perjury, that the complaining party is authorized to act on behalf of the owner of an exclusive right that is allegedly infringed. Fertile Soul's Designated Agent is:Jesse Johnson11359 Main StRoscoe, IL 61073TrademarksFertile Soul owns trademarks for its many goods and services, including without limitation, The Fertile Soul MethodTM and Fertile Soul RetreatsTM. These and other Fertile Soul graphics, logos and service marks are trademarks of Fertile Soul and may not be used without prior written consent of Fertile Soul. All other trademarks, product names, and company names and logos appearing on this Website are the property of their respective owners.Ideas and InventionsAll comments, feedback, suggestions, ideas, and other submissions (“Ideas”) disclosed, submitted, or offered to Fertile Soul in connection with your use of this Website shall be the exclusive property of the Fertile Soul. User agrees that unless otherwise prohibited by law Fertile Soul may use, sell, exploit and disclose the Ideas in any manner, without restriction and without compensation to User.LinkingIf you have a website and wish to establish temporary or permanent links from your website to this Website, you must request and receive written permission from us.5. PRIVACY AND PROTECTION OF PERSONAL INFORMATIONFertile Soul respects the privacy of visitors to our Website. Please see Fertile Soul's Privacy Policy relating to the collection and use of your information. User acknowledges and agrees that this Privacy Policy, including but not limited to the manner in which Fertile Soul collects, uses and discloses User’s personally identifiable information, is incorporated and made part of these Terms of Use. If User does not agree to each and every part of Fertile Soul's Privacy Policy, then User should not use this site or submit or post any personally identifiable information on this site. Questions regarding Website privacy issues should be directed to Fertile Soul's Webmaster at info@thefertilesoul.com.6. DISCLAIMERS AND LIMITATION OF LIABILITYUser expressly agrees that use of Fertile Soul's Website and service is at User’s sole risk. Neither Fertile Soul, nor its affiliates, nor any of their officers, directors, or employees, agents, third-party content providers, merchants, sponsors, licensors (collectively, “Providers”), or the like, warrant that websites affiliated with Fertile Soul, including but not limited to this Website, will be uninterrupted, error-free, or free of viruses, worms, Trojan horses, keyboard loggers, spyware, adware, malware, harmful or malicious code, or other defects. The information, products and services published on this Website may contain inaccuracies or typographical errors. The Providers make no warranty as to the results that may be obtained from the use of Fertile Soul's Website or as to the accuracy, reliability, or currency of any information content, service, or merchandise provided through Fertile Soul's Website.A. Disclaimer of WarrantiesTHIS WEBSITE IS PROVIDED BY FERTILE SOUL ON AN “AS IS” AND “AS AVAILABLE” BASIS. TO THE FULLEST EXTENT PERMISSIBLE BY APPLICABLE LAW, FERTILE SOUL AND THE PROVIDERS DISCLAIM ALL IMPLIED WARRANTIES, INCLUDING BUT NOT LIMITED TO, IMPLIED AND STATUTORY WARRANTIES OF MERCHANTABILITY, FITNESS FOR A PARTICULAR PURPOSE, AND NON-INFRINGEMENT OF PROPRIETARY RIGHTS.FERTILE SOUL AND THE PROVIDERS MAKE NO REPRESENTATIONS OR WARRANTIES OF ANY KIND, EXPRESS OR IMPLIED, AS TO THE OPERATION OF THE WEBSITE, SECURITY OF THE WEBSITE, THE AVAILABILITY OF ANY SERVICES OFFERED ON OR THROUGH THE WEBSITE, OR THE INFORMATION, CONTENT, MATERIALS OR PRODUCTS, INCLUDED ON THIS WEBSITE. ANY MATERIALS DOWNLOADED OR OTHERWISE OBTAINED THROUGH THE USE OF THE WEBSITE IS DONE AT YOUR OWN DISCRETION AND RISK AND THAT YOU WILL BE SOLELY RESPONSIBLE FOR ANY DAMAGE TO YOUR COMPUTER SYSTEM OR LOSS OF DATA THAT RESULTS FROM THE DOWNLOAD OF ANY SUCH MATERIAL. YOU EXPRESSLY AGREE THAT YOUR USE OF THIS WEBSITE IS AT YOUR SOLE RISK.NO ORAL ADVICE OR WRITTEN INFORMATION GIVEN BY FERTILE SOUL NOR ITS AFFILIATES, NOR ANY OF THEIR OFFICERS, DIRECTORS, EMPLOYEES, AGENTS, PROVIDERS, OR THE LIKE, SHALL CREATE A WARRANTY OF ANY KIND; NOR SHALL USER RELY ON ANY SUCH INFORMATION OR ADVICE.SOME STATES OR OTHER JURISDICTIONS DO NOT ALLOW THE EXCLUSION OF IMPLIED WARRANTIES, SO THE ABOVE EXCLUSIONS MAY NOT APPLY TO YOU. YOU MAY ALSO HAVE OTHER RIGHTS THAT VARY FROM STATE TO STATE AND JURISDICTION TO JURISDICTION.If you are dissatisfied with this Website and/or Materials, your sole and exclusive remedy is to discontinue your use of this Website.B. Limitation of LiabilityFERTILE SOUL DOES NOT GUARANTEE THE CONTINUOUS, UNINTERRUPTED OR SECURE ACCESS TO THIS WEBSITE OR ANY RELATED SERVICES. THE OPERATION OF THIS WEBSITE MAY BE INTERFERED WITH BY NUMEROUS FACTORS OUTSIDE THE CONTROL OF FERTILE SOUL.YOU EXPRESSLY UNDERSTAND AND AGREE THAT FERTILE SOUL AND THE PROVIDERS WILL NOT BE LIABLE FOR ANY DAMAGES OF ANY KIND ARISING FROM THE USE OF OR INABILITY TO USE THIS WEBSITE, INCLUDING BUT NOT LIMITED TO DIRECT, INDIRECT, INCIDENTAL, CONSEQUENTIAL, SPECIAL, EXEMPLARY, AND PUNITIVE DAMAGES WHETHER SUCH CLAIM IS BASED ON WARRANTY, CONTRACT, TORT (INCLUDING NEGLIGENCE), OR OTHERWISE, (EVEN IF FERTILE SOUL OR ITS PROVIDERS HAVE BEEN ADVISED OF THE POSSIBILITY OF SUCH DAMAGES).THE LIMITATIONS OF THIS PARAGRAPH SHALL APPLY NOTWITHSTANDING ANY RELIANCE BY A USER ON ANY INFORMATION OBTAINED FROM THIS WEBSITE OR OTHER FERTILE SOUL WEBSITES THAT RESULT FROM MISTAKES, OMISSIONS, INTERRUPTIONS, DELETION OF FILES OR E-MAIL, ERRORS, DEFECTS, VIRUSES OR OTHER MALICIOUS CODE, DELAYS IN OPERATION OR TRANSMISSION, OR ANY FAILURE OF PERFORMANCE, WHETHER OR NOT RESULTING FROM ACTS OF GOD, COMMUNICATIONS FAILURE, THEFT, DESTRUCTION, OR UNAUTHORIZED ACCESS TO FERTILE SOUL'S RECORDS, PROGRAMS, OR SERVICES, AND WHETHER OR NOT FERTILE SOUL AND/OR ANY OTHER PROVIDERS HAVE BEEN ADVISED OF THE POSSIBILITY OF SUCH DAMAGES. USER HEREBY ACKNOWLEDGES THAT THIS PARAGRAPH SHALL APPLY TO ALL CONTENT, MERCHANDISE, AND SERVICES AVAILABLE THROUGH THIS WEBSITE.SUCH LIMITATION OF LIABILITY SHALL APPLY WHETHER THE DAMAGES ARISE FROM USE OR MISUSE OF AND RELIANCE ON THE FERTILE SOUL SERVICES, FROM INABILITY TO USE THE FERTILE SOUL SERVICES, OR FROM THE INTERRUPTION, SUSPENSION, OR TERMINATION OF THE FERTILE SOUL SERVICES (INCLUDING SUCH DAMAGES INCURRED BY THIRD PARTIES).SOME STATES OR OTHER JURISDICTIONS DO NOT ALLOW THE EXCLUSION OR LIMITATION OF LIABILITY FOR INCIDENTAL OR CONSEQUENTIAL DAMAGES, SO THE ABOVE LIMITATIONS AND EXCLUSIONS MAY NOT APPLY TO YOU.If you are dissatisfied with this Website and/or Materials, your sole and exclusive remedy is to discontinue your use of this Website.7. ONLINE CONDUCTThe User agrees to use this Website only for lawful purposes. Unacceptable uses of the Website include without limitation: (i) engaging in any illegal activity or the planning of any illegal activity; (ii) disseminating or transmitting statements or material that, to a reasonable person, may be abusive, obscene, pornographic, defamatory, harassing, grossly offensive, vulgar, threatening or malicious; (iii) creating, disseminating or transmitting files, graphics, software or other material that actually or potentially infringes the copyright, trademark, patent, trade secret, publicity or other intellectual property rights of any person; (iv) creating a false identity or otherwise attempting to mislead any person as to the identity or origin of any communication; (v) exporting, re-exporting or permitting the downloading of any message, software or content in violation of any export or import law, regulation or restriction of the United States and its agencies or authorities, or without all required approvals, licenses or exemptions; (vi) interfering, disrupting or attempting to gain unauthorized access to other accounts on the Website or any other computer network; (vii) disseminating or transmitting viruses, worms, Trojan horses, RATs, keyboard loggers, time bombs, spyware, adware, cancelbots or any other malicious or invasive code or program; or (viii) engaging in any other activity deemed by The Fertile Soul to be in conflict with the spirit or intent of this Website.8. TERMINATIONThese Terms of Use are effective until terminated by either party. You may terminate these terms at any time by discontinuing use of the this Website and destroying all Materials obtained from this Website and all copies thereof, whether made under these Terms of Use or otherwise. Your access to the this Website may be terminated immediately without notice from The Fertile Soul if in our sole discretion you fail to comply with any term or provision of these Terms of Use. Upon termination, you must cease use of this Website and destroy all Materials obtained from this Website and all copies thereof, whether made under these Terms of Use or otherwise.9. INTERNATIONAL USERSThis Website can be accessed from locations around the world. Fertile Soul makes no representations that this Website or the Materials available through it are appropriate for use at other locations outside the United States. Access to this Website from locations where this Website or any of its Materials are illegal is prohibited. If you access this Website from a location outside the United States, you are responsible for compliance with all local and/or international laws.10. SECURITYIf you use this Website, you are responsible for restricting access to your computer and ensuring that your computer is free from all types of malicious code, spyware, viruses, Trojans, etc. that may track any data you enter via this Website.Fertile Soul reserves the right to monitor all network traffic to this Website to identify and/or block unauthorized attempts or intrusions to upload or change information or cause damage to this Website in any fashion. Anyone using this Website expressly consents to such monitoring.11. ARBITRATIONAny dispute relating in any way to your visit to Website shall be submitted to confidential arbitration in North Carolina, except that, to the extent you have in any manner violated or threatened to violate Fertile Soul intellectual property rights, Fertile Soul may seek injunctive, equitable, or other appropriate relief in any state or federal court and the User consents to exclusive jurisdiction and venue in the states and federal courts in the State of North Carolina.  Arbitration under this agreement shall be conducted under the rules then prevailing of the American Arbitration Association (www.adr.org). The arbitrator’s award, including attorneys’ fees, shall be binding and may be entered as a judgment in any court of competent jurisdiction. To the fullest extent permitted by applicable law, no arbitration under these Terms of Use or Privacy Policy shall be joined to an arbitration involving any other party subject to these Terms of Use or Privacy Policy, whether through class arbitration proceedings or otherwise.12. APPLICABLE LAW/JURISDICTIONThis Website is controlled by Fertile Soul from its offices in the State of North Carolina.  As such, by visiting Fertile Soul's Website, even if accessed from a location outside the United States, you agree that the laws of the State of North Carolina will govern these disclaimers, terms of use, and privacy statement, without giving effect to any principles of conflicts of laws. Fertile Soul reserves the right to make changes to its Website and these disclaimers, terms of use, and privacy statement at any time. User hereby irrevocably and unconditionally consents to jurisdiction in the State of North Carolina.13. WAIVER/SEVERABILITYThe failure of Fertile Soul to require or enforce strict performance by User of any provision of these Terms of Use or to exercise any right under them shall not be construed as a waiver or relinquishment of Fertile Soul's right to assert or rely upon any such provision or right in that or any other instance.The provisions of these Terms of Use are intended to be severable. If for any reason any provision of these Terms of Use shall be held invalid or unenforceable in whole or in part by any court of competent jurisdiction, such provision shall, as to such jurisdiction, be ineffective to the extent of such determination of invalidity or unenforceability without affecting the validity or enforceability thereof in any other manner and without affecting the remaining provisions hereof, which shall continue to be in full force and effect.14. STATUTE OF LIMITATIONSYou agree that regardless of any statute or law to the contrary, any claim or cause of action arising out of or related to use of this Website, Terms of Use, or Privacy Policy must be filed within ONE (1) YEAR after such claim or cause of action arose or be forever barred.15. ENTIRE AGREEMENTThese Terms of Use constitute the entire agreement between the User and Fertile Soul with respect to the subject matter hereof and supersedes and replaces all prior or contemporaneous understandings or agreements, written or oral, regarding such subject matter. Any waiver of any provision of the Terms of Use or Privacy Policy will be effective only if in writing and signed by Fertile Soul.THE SECTION TITLES IN THE TERMS OF USE AND PRIVACY POLICY ARE FOR CONVENIENCE ONLY AND HAVE NO LEGAL OR CONTRACTUAL EFFECT.THESE TERMS OF USE MAY BE CHANGED AT ANY TIME, WITHOUT PRIOR NOTICE TO ANY VISITOR
Terms and Conditions
Website Policy
HIPPA Policy
Cancellation Policy
